{
  "apikey": "%PUT-YOUR-API-KEY-HERE%",
  "description": "This is simple calibration data used for testing purposes. Do not use it in production environment!",
  "copyright": "Copyright (C) 2238 by BanAN Technologies Inc.",
  "test-data": [
    {
      "question": "92 + 90",
      "answer": 182
    },
    {
      "question": "81 + 90",
      "answer": 171
    },
    {
      "question": "77 + 30",
      "answer": 107
    },
    {
      "question": "38 + 14",
      "answer": 52
    },
    {
      "question": "3 + 82",
      "answer": 85
    },
    {
      "question": "33 + 92",
      "answer": 125
    },
    {
      "question": "7 + 56",
      "answer": 63
    },
    {
      "question": "30 + 99",
      "answer": 129
    },
    {
      "question": "25 + 4",
      "answer": 29
    },
    {
      "question": "17 + 40",
      "answer": 57
    },
    {
      "question": "9 + 19",
      "answer": 28
    },
    {
      "question": "79 + 74",
      "answer": 153
    },
    {
      "question": "79 + 77",
      "answer": 156
    },
    {
      "question": "30 + 91",
      "answer": 121
    },
    {
      "question": "14 + 69",
      "answer": 83
    },
    {
      "question": "37 + 91",
      "answer": 128
    },
    {
      "question": "18 + 74",
      "answer": 92
    },
    {
      "question": "56 + 75",
      "answer": 131
    },
    {
      "question": "47 + 74",
      "answer": 121
    },
    {
      "question": "44 + 52",
      "answer": 96
    },
    {
      "question": "63 + 43",
      "answer": 106
    },
    {
      "question": "58 + 76",
      "answer": 134
    },
    {
      "question": "94 + 40",
      "answer": 134
    },
    {
      "question": "80 + 63",
      "answer": 143
    },
    {
      "question": "70 + 19",
      "answer": 89
    },
    {
      "question": "49 + 10",
      "answer": 59
    },
    {
      "question": "81 + 89",
      "answer": 170
    },
    {
      "question": "32 + 56",
      "answer": 88
    },
    {
      "question": "8 + 12",
      "answer": 20
    },
    {
      "question": "85 + 10",
      "answer": 95
    },
    {
      "question": "53 + 91",
      "answer": 144
    },
    {
      "question": "65 + 26",
      "answer": 91
    },
    {
      "question": "95 + 23",
      "answer": 118
    },
    {
      "question": "45 + 48",
      "answer": 93
    },
    {
      "question": "29 + 93",
      "answer": 122
    },
    {
      "question": "38 + 82",
      "answer": 120
    },
    {
      "question": "61 + 94",
      "answer": 155
    },
    {
      "question": "16 + 22",
      "answer": 38
    },
    {
      "question": "67 + 67",
      "answer": 134
    },
    {
      "question": "13 + 94",
      "answer": 107
    },
    {
      "question": "5 + 58",
      "answer": 63
    },
    {
      "question": "88 + 30",
      "answer": 118
    },
    {
      "question": "86 + 82",
      "answer": 168
    },
    {
      "question": "58 + 89",
      "answer": 147
    },
    {
      "question": "61 + 12",
      "answer": 73
    },
    {
      "question": "95 + 21",
      "answer": 116
    },
    {
      "question": "15 + 90",
      "answer": 105
    },
    {
      "question": "50 + 68",
      "answer": 118
    },
    {
      "question": "19 + 72",
      "answer": 91
    },
    {
      "question": "23 + 15",
      "answer": 38
    },
    {
      "question": "40 + 89",
      "answer": 129
    },
    {
      "question": "5 + 36",
      "answer": 41
    },
    {
      "question": "62 + 51",
      "answer": 113
    },
    {
      "question": "1 + 29",
      "answer": 30
    },
    {
      "question": "66 + 75",
      "answer": 141
    },
    {
      "question": "97 + 41",
      "answer": 138
    },
    {
      "question": "1 + 78",
      "answer": 79
    },
    {
      "question": "84 + 10",
      "answer": 94
    },
    {
      "question": "83 + 69",
      "answer": 152
    },
    {
      "question": "29 + 83",
      "answer": 112
    },
    {
      "question": "73 + 68",
      "answer": 141
    },
    {
      "question": "90 + 23",
      "answer": 113
    },
    {
      "question": "78 + 37",
      "answer": 115
    },
    {
      "question": "14 + 86",
      "answer": 100
    },
    {
      "question": "39 + 40",
      "answer": 79
    },
    {
      "question": "56 + 13",
      "answer": 69
    },
    {
      "question": "23 + 53",
      "answer": 76
    },
    {
      "question": "11 + 62",
      "answer": 73
    },
    {
      "question": "44 + 85",
      "answer": 129
    },
    {
      "question": "22 + 74",
      "answer": 96
    },
    {
      "question": "40 + 50",
      "answer": 90
    },
    {
      "question": "7 + 89",
      "answer": 96
    },
    {
      "question": "26 + 91",
      "answer": 117
    },
    {
      "question": "44 + 50",
      "answer": 94
    },
    {
      "question": "57 + 59",
      "answer": 116
    },
    {
      "question": "80 + 65",
      "answer": 145
    },
    {
      "question": "55 + 5",
      "answer": 60
    },
    {
      "question": "74 + 25",
      "answer": 99
    },
    {
      "question": "37 + 94",
      "answer": 131
    },
    {
      "question": "84 + 35",
      "answer": 119
    },
    {
      "question": "56 + 35",
      "answer": 91
    },
    {
      "question": "88 + 37",
      "answer": 125
    },
    {
      "question": "27 + 83",
      "answer": 110
    },
    {
      "question": "58 + 47",
      "answer": 105
    },
    {
      "question": "87 + 49",
      "answer": 136
    },
    {
      "question": "89 + 85",
      "answer": 174
    },
    {
      "question": "35 + 58",
      "answer": 93
    },
    {
      "question": "83 + 95",
      "answer": 178
    },
    {
      "question": "67 + 64",
      "answer": 131
    },
    {
      "question": "42 + 80",
      "answer": 122
    },
    {
      "question": "46 + 72",
      "answer": 118
    },
    {
      "question": "48 + 99",
      "answer": 147
    },
    {
      "question": "67 + 85",
      "answer": 152
    },
    {
      "question": "6 + 78",
      "answer": 84
    },
    {
      "question": "56 + 5",
      "answer": 61
    },
    {
      "question": "23 + 53",
      "answer": 76
    },
    {
      "question": "65 + 85",
      "answer": 150
    },
    {
      "question": "25 + 73",
      "answer": 98
    },
    {
      "question": "87 + 89",
      "answer": 176
    },
    {
      "question": "80 + 48",
      "answer": 128
    }
  ],
  "chunk": {
    "number": 21,
    "total": 22,
    "size": 100,
    "range": {
      "from": 2000,
      "to": 2100
    }
  }
}